http://www.ezyearbooks.com/privacy

Service Request Form
Have a Suggestion?
Service Request Form
Have a Suggestion?
Privacy Statement
This is an alert notification for the Pascoag Utility District. It can be enabled, disabled, and edited as needed.
We are committed to protecting your privacy. The information we collect is gathered to ensure secure payments. See below for detailed information about how we protect your personal information. If you have any concerns, comments or complaints, be sure to let us know.
We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal information as required by law or to protect PUD, its customers, or the public. At any time you may contact PUD with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the data you have given us and request correction or deletion.
How We Use Your Personal Information
Information we collect may be used in the following ways:
To complete your transactions
To bill your credit card for your payments as initiated and authorized by you
To confirm your payments
To respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests
To communicate offers and special information to you, if you choose to receive such notices
To customize your experience on our web site
PUD requires only the personal information that is needed for safely processing your online payment and for contacting you about your transactions. It is used exclusively for that purpose. As an PUD customer, you may receive email from us based on your account information and your account information may be analyzed as part of our standard business practices.
When you make a payment online from PUD, we may contact you by e-mail to confirm your payment and to update you on the status of your payment.
Protecting Your Information
We employ powerful 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (SSL) in all areas where your personal identity is required. Your account information and order history are kept behind our firewall. All transaction information is processed under encrypted channels. To be sure you have the most protection available, be sure to download the latest version of today’s most popular browsers, Microsoft Internet Explorer and Netscape Communicator.
Only authorized personnel at PUD are permitted to see your password. If you forget your password, you can receive a reminder via e-mail. Only authorized customer service and accounting personnel are permitted access to your account information. Employees who violate our privacy pledge will be subject to our normal disciplinary process.
If we change how we use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the change to this site.
Pay My Bill
Pascoag Utility District offers the latest technology to help you manage your electric or water account 24/7 by computer, smartphone or tablet with a free online application called SmartHub.Learn more about SmartHub
One Time Payment
No registration Required
Pay Bill/View Usage
Registration Required
Community
Calendar of Events
2013 photos
Photo Archives
Phase 3 Cleaning and Lining Project to begin March 30th-What you need to know
© 2008-2020 Pascoag Utility District. All Rights Reserved.Non-Discrimination StatementPrivacy StatementPayment Conditions
